Killers for hire are paid for what they can do, not
for what they believe... until today.
Men of War is a action, drama, thriller film directed by Perry Lang.
Nick Gunar is a burnt-out, jaded and hard-up former mercenary who is
having a difficult time adjusting to civilian life.
At the end of his rope, he is hired by the Nitro Mine Corporation to strong-arm the natives of a
South China Sea island into giving up their rights to its valuable mineral resources.
Nick loathes the thought of another mission, but this seemingly easy job will
earn him enough money to get back with his estranged family.
He recruits some of his former mercenary buddies to help him with the job.
The island people refuse to give up their land and Nick decides to
help them fight the greedy corporation that hired him.
As greed and treachery begin to unravel, Nick's
band of mercenaries choose sides.
Nick Gunar, played by Dolph Lundgren.
Loki, played by Charlotte Lewis.
Po, played by BD Wong.
Ocker, played by Tim Guinee.
Grace Lashield, played by Catherine Bell.
Keefer, played by Trevor Goddard.
Men of War is a 1994 action film directed by Perry Lang, written by
John Sayles, and revised by Ethan Reiff and Cyrus Voris.
It stars Dolph Lundgren as Nick Gunar, a former Special Ops soldier who leads a
group of mercenaries to a treasure island in the South China Sea.
The film explores themes of island, martial arts, showdown, asia, village.
The tone is emotional and intense.